Cody's not just growing up... he's growing fins!
The Thirteenth Year is a tv movie, adventure,
comedy film directed by Duwayne Dunham.
A teen learns that his birth mother is a mermaid after he begins to
grow fins and slimy scales on his thirteenth birthday.
Cody Griffin, played by Chez Starbuck.
Jess Wheatley, played by Justin Jon Ross.
Sam, played by Courtnee Draper.
Whit Griffin, played by Dave Coulier.
Girl in Fountain Line (uncredited), played by Kristen Stewart.
Sean Marshall, played by Tim Redwine.
The Thirteenth Year is a 1999 American fantasy comedy film directed by
Duwayne Dunham and starring Chez Starbuck and Courtnee Draper.
It premiered on Disney Channel on May 15, 1999.
The film explores themes of parent child relationship,
birthday, fishing, mermaid, adopted.
The tone is lighthearted.